Yay! Yay!
Congratulations!
♪ background music
Pa-pa-pa! Pa-pa-pa!
You want to do it here?
Sure thing.
♪ background music
Everybody.
Merchandise bags.
You're the guy who puts the product bags in the plastic bags.
We just met!
I thought you were Comic-Co! I thought you were Comic-Co!
No offense.
It was too comical.
I'll think of something.
You're right.
♪ BGM ♪
What a great feeling.
It's like...
♪ background music
Let's have some fun.
It's probably been a long time since I've been to a show.
I think you'll be surprised to see me at the show.
Maybe you'll remember.
For the first time.
First time.
Let's just focus and have fun.
Go on.
Aah!
Yes, it's gone!
Cheers
(BGM)
Go! I'm coming out!
Shut up! Shut up!
♪ background music
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no!
(background music)
(cheering)
Oh!
Cheers
♪ background music
It's hot.
Okay, then
Mr. Radio Group
We've been here since yesterday.
We're all here.
New members.
It was the first time for me to come back.
I thought it was going to be a bit of a bumpy ride.
I'm so happy to see how warm everyone is.
It's so great.
Have fun dancing!
Happy!
Everybody's happy.
♪ BGM
♪ Cheers from the crowd
♪ background music
Yes, thank you very much.
I'm number 7, Mike Amasawa Tulito.
Mr. Tulito.
Ah.
Yes, thank you.
♪ BGM
♪ background music
A little look at today's timing
Aww, he's cute
I'll say hello as I check it out
Right around. Right around.
Here we go.
Mike Soft, bring it to the world!
Seven-Eleven-Eleven.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
New style
♪ BGM
Yay
♪ background music
Thank you.
The best
The best.
Awesome.
In a new way.
♪ Music ♪
I'm so happy.
Debut.
Wow!
First time
Yay.
Oh, my God.
How's it going? Before you go...
Yeah!
Laughs.
♪ background music ♪
♪ background music
Your dad's gonna love this look.
Daddy.
Laughs.
♪ background music ♪
Good morning
(background music)
Wow.
♪ background music
The best
Good job.
That's hot.
You know what?
Excuse me.
Um...
Good morning.
Good morning
BGM
♪ background music
LOL
Good
Good.
LOL
LOL!
I edited it a little bit.
It's kind of weird.
LOL!
LOL.
I got something weird.
Something weird came out.
I got a weird one.
I got a weird one
I got a weird one!
BGM
The first one
Before it starts
With the music.
LOL!
Teren, Teren, Ten.
I'm a college student.College student.
Teren, ten, ten, ten.
BGM
Teren, Ten, Ten, Ten, Ten
Yes, sir.
BGM
Ta-da!
YOSHII-CHAN
BGM
Teren, teren, teren, teren, teren, teren, teren
Bye bye bye
BGM
Bye, bye, bye.